IUE-CWA Local 301; Records apap023
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1939-2003; 5; 854
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 November 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 November 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 November 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 November 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 November 28
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 December 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 December 7
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 December 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 December 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 December 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 December 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1949 December 30
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 January 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 January 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 January 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 January 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 February 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 February 10
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 February 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 February 17
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 February 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 March 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 March 10
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 March 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 March 17
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 March 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 March 31
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 April 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 April 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 April 28
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 May 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 May 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 May 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 May 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 May 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 May 26
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 June 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 June 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 June 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 June 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 June 30
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 July 7
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 July 7
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 July 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 July 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 July 28
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 August 4
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 August 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 August 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 August 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 October 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 October 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 November 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 November 17
  - Electrical Union News, 1950 December 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 January 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 February 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 February 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 March 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 March 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 March 30
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 April 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 May 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 May 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 May 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 June 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 June 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 July 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 July 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 August 10
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 August 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 August 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 August 31
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 September 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 September 7
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 September 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 September 28
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 October 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 October 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 October 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 October 26
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 November 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 November 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 November 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 November 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 November 30
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 December 7
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 December 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1951 December 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 January 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 January 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 January 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 February 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 February 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 February 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 February 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 February 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 March 7
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 March 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 March 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 March 28
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 April 4
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 April 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 April 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 April 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 May 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 May 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 May 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 May 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 May 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 June 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 June 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 June 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 June 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 July 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 July 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 July 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 July 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 August 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 August 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 August 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 August 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 September 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 September 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 September 26
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 October 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 October 10
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 October 17
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 October 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 October 31
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 November 7
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 November 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 November 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 November 28
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 December 4
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 December 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1952 December 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 January 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 January 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 January 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 January 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 January 30
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 February 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 February 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 February 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 February 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 March 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 March 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 March 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 March 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 April 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 April 10
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 April 17
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 April 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 May 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 May 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 May 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 May 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 May 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 June 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 June 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 June 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 June 26
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 July 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 July 10
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 July 17
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 July 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 July 31
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 August 7
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 August 14
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 August 21
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 August 28
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 September 4
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 September 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 September 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 October 2
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 October 9
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 October 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 October 23
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 October 30
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 November 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 November 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 November 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 December 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 December 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1953 December 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 January 8
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 January 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 January 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 February 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 February 11
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 February 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 February 26
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 March 5
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 March 12
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 March 16
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 March 18
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 March 19
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 March 25
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 March 26
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 April 1
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 April 15
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 April 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 April 29
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 May 6
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 May 13
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 May 20
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 May 27
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 June 3
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 June 10
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 June 17
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 June 24
  - Electrical Union News, 1954 December 22
  - Electrical Union News, 1959 December 9
  - Electrical Union News, Undated
  - IUE-CIO News, 1950 February 7
  - IUE-CIO News, 1950 February 21
  - IUE-CIO News, 1950 February 28
  - IUE-CIO News, 1950 March 5
  - IUE-CIO News, 1950 March 17
  - IUE-CIO News, 1950 March 27
  - IUE-CIO News, 1950 April 4
  - IUE-CIO News, 1950 April 11
  - IUE-CIO News, 1950 April 20
  - IUE-CIO News, 1950 April 27
  - IUE-CIO News, 1950 May 5
  - IUE-CIO News, 1950 May 12
  - IUE-CIO News, 1950 May 19
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 March 22
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 March 29
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 April 12
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 April 19
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 April 26
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 May 10
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 May 17
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 May 24
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 May 31
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 June 7
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 June 18
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 June 21
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 June 28
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 July 5
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 July 12
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 July 19
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 August 2
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 August 9
  - IUE-CIO News, 1951 September 13
  - IUE-CIO News, 1953 August 23
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 April 2
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 April 9
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 April 16
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 April 23
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 April 30
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 May 7
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 May 14
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 May 19
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 May 21
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 May 26
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 May 28
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 June 4
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 June 18
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 June 23
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 June 25
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 July 2
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 July 9
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 July 16
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 August 2
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 August 6
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 August 13
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 August 20
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 August 27
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 September 3
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 September 10
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 September 17
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 October 1
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 October 8
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 October 15
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 October 22
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 October 29
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 November 5
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 November 12
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 November 19
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 December 3
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 December 10
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1954 December 31
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 January 7
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 January 14
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 January 21
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 February 11
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 February 25
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 March 11
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 March 25
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 April 8
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 April 22
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 May 6
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 May 20
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 June 3
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 June 17
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 July 1
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 July 15
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 August 12
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 August 26
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 September 9
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 September 23
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 October 7
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 October 21
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 November 4
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 November 18
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 December 2
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 December 16
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1955 December 30
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 January 27
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 February 10
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 February 24
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 March 9
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 March 23
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 April 6
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 April 20
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 May 4
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 May 18
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 June 8
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 June 22
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 July 20
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 August 10
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 August 24
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 September 7
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 September 21
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 October 5
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 October 19
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 November 2
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 November 16
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 November 30
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1956 December 21
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 January 11
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 January 25
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 February 8
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 February 21
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 March 8
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 March 22
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 April 5
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 April 19
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 May 3
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 May 17
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 June 7
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 June 21
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 July 12
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 August 2
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 August 30
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 September 13
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 September 27
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 October 11
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 October 25
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 November 8
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 December 6
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1957 December 20
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 January 10
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 January 24
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 February 7
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 February 28
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 March 14
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 March 28
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 April 18
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 May 2
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 May 16
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 May 29
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 June 13
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 June 27
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 July 11
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 August 8
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 August 29
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 September 12
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 October 3
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 October 17
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 October 31
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 November 14
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1958 December 12
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 January 16
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 February 6
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 February 27
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 March 6
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 March 11
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 March 20
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 March 27
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 April 3
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 April 10
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 April 24
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 April
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 May 1
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 May 8
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 May 15
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 May 22
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 June 5
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 June 12
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 June 19
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 June 26
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 July 10
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 July 17
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 July 24
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 July 31
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 August 7
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 August 14
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 August 21
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 August 28
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 September 4
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 September 11
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 September 18
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 September 25
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 October 2
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 October 6
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 October 16
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 October 23
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 October 30
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 November 13
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 November 20
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 November 27
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 December 4
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 December 11
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1959 December 18
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 January 6
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 January 15
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 January 22
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 January 29
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 February 5
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 February 12
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 February 19
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 February 26
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 March 4
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 March 11
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 March 18
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 March 25
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 April 1
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 April 8
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 April 15
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 April 22
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 April 29
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 May 6
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 May 13
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 May 20
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 May 27
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 June 3
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 June 10
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 June 17
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 June 24
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 July 1
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 July 8
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 July 22
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 July 29
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 August 5
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 August 12
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 August 19
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 August 26
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 September 2
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 September 9
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 September 16
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 September 22
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 October 21
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 November 11
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 November 25
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 December 2
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 December 16
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 December 23
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1960 December 30
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 January 6
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 January 13
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 January 20
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 January 27
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 February 3
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 February 10
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 February 17
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 February 24
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 March 3
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 March 10
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 March 17
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 March 24
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 March 31
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 April 7
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 April 14
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 April 21
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 April 28
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 May 5
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 May 12
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 May 19
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 May 26
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 June 2
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 June 9
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 June 16
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 June 23
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 June 30
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 July 14
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 July 21
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 July 28
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 August 4
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 August 11
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 August 18
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 August 25
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 September 1
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 September 8
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 September 15
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 September 22
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 September 29
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 October 6
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 October 13
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 October 20
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 October 27
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 November 10
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 November 17
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 November 24
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 December 1
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 December 8
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 December 15
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1961 December 29
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 January 5
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 January 12
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 January 19
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 January 26
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 February 2
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 February 9
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 February 16
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 February 23
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 March 2
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 March 9
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 March 13
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 March 16
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 March 23
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 March 30
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 April 6
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 April 20
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 April 27
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 May 4
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 May 11
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 May 18
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 May 25
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 June 1
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 June 8
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 June 15
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 June 22
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 June 29
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 July 6
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 July 13
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 July 20
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 July 27
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 August 3
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 August 10
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 August 17
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 August 24
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 August 31
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 September 5
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 September 12
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 September 14
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 September 21
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 September 28
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 October 19
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 October 26
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 November 2
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 November 9
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 November 16
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 November 23
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 November 30
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 December 7
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 December 14
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, 1962 December 21
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, Undated
  - Atomic Workers News, 1953 August 24
  - Congressional Record, 1950 January 16
  - Daily Evening, 1953 April
  - UE Local 301 News, Microfilm, 1947 April-1954 June (Microfilm 1)
  - IUE-CIO Local 301 News, Microfilm, 1954 April 2 - 1990 June (Microfilm 2)
  - Electrical Union News Local 301, 1947 April 25-1954 June 29 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 1)
  - IUE Local 301 News, 1954 April 2-1966 December 28 (Box 2 (5-Publications), Folder 1)